Here, we have a constructor function called Developer,
لدينا هنا دالة منشئ تُسمى "Developer"،
which we can invoke to set up a new object,
والتي يمكننا استدعائها لإعداد كائن جديد،
with a single name property. Let's go ahead and do that.
مع خاصية أحادية الاسم. لنتابع ونفعل هذا.
So, we just called the Developer constructor function using the new keyword.
لذلك، لقد قمنا باستدعاء دالة المنشئ "Developer" باستخدام الكلمة الأساسية الجديدة.
And pass it a string, Veronika,
وتمريرها سلسلة، Veronika،
which will be the value of the object's name property.
والتي ستكون قيمة خاصية اسم الكائن.
Let's double check to see if this is indeed an object.
دعونا نتحقق مرة أخرى لنرى إذا كان ذلك كائنًا بحق.
And indeed, it is.
وبالفعل، هو كذلك.
Now, we can use the instance of method to
يمكننا الآن أن نستخدم مثيل الأسلوب
check if it's an instance of the Developer constructor function.
للتحقق مما إذا كان مثيل دالة المنشئ "Developer".
Using the instance of operator returns a boolean.
يؤدي استخدام مثيل المشغل إلى إرجاع قيمة منطقية.
So, we can see that it's indeed true.
لذلك، يمكننا أن نرى أنه صحيح بالفعل.
One thing to keep in mind here is that,
هناك أمر واحد عليكم مراعاته وهو،
you don't want to put parentheses at the end of the function name over here.
أنكم لستم بحاجة إلى وضع أقواس بنهاية اسم الدالة هنا.
We're not invoking the Developer constructor function,
حيث أننا لا نقوم باستدعاء دالة المنشئ "Developer"،
we are just referring to it by name.
بل نشير إليها باستخدام الاسم فحسب.